(function(){const t=document.createElement("link").relList;if(t&&t.supports&&t.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const s of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))r(s);new MutationObserver(s=>{for(const o of s)if(o.type==="childList")for(const i of o.addedNodes)i.tagName==="LINK"&&i.rel==="modulepreload"&&r(i)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function n(s){const o={};return s.integrity&&(o.integrity=s.integrity),s.referrerPolicy&&(o.referrerPolicy=s.referrerPolicy),s.crossOrigin==="use-credentials"?o.credentials="include":s.crossOrigin==="anonymous"?o.credentials="omit":o.credentials="same-origin",o}function r(s){if(s.ep)return;s.ep=!0;const o=n(s);fetch(s.href,o)}})();function I(){}function H(e){return e()}function C(){return Object.create(null)}function $(e){e.forEach(H)}function S(e){return typeof e=="function"}function R(e,t){return e!=e?t==t:e!==t||e&&typeof e=="object"||typeof e=="function"}function K(e){return Object.keys(e).length===0}function m(e,t){e.appendChild(t)}function D(e,t,n){e.insertBefore(t,n||null)}function P(e){e.parentNode&&e.parentNode.removeChild(e)}function g(e){return document.createElement(e)}function J(e){return document.createTextNode(e)}function E(){return J(" ")}function Y(e,t,n,r){return e.addEventListener(t,n,r),()=>e.removeEventListener(t,n,r)}function k(e,t,n){n==null?e.removeAttribute(t):e.getAttribute(t)!==n&&e.setAttribute(t,n)}function W(e){return Array.from(e.childNodes)}function T(e,t){t=""+t,e.data!==t&&(e.data=t)}let j;function q(e){j=e}const v=[],L=[];let x=[];const z=[],G=Promise.resolve();let A=!1;function U(){A||(A=!0,G.then(M))}function O(e){x.push(e)}const N=new Set;let _=0;function M(){if(_!==0)return;const e=j;do{try{for(;_<v.length;){const t=v[_];_++,q(t),V(t.$$)}}catch(t){throw v.length=0,_=0,t}for(q(null),v.length=0,_=0;L.length;)L.pop()();for(let t=0;t<x.length;t+=1){const n=x[t];N.has(n)||(N.add(n),n())}x.length=0}while(v.length);for(;z.length;)z.pop()();A=!1,N.clear(),q(e)}function V(e){if(e.fragment!==null){e.update(),$(e.before_update);const t=e.dirty;e.dirty=[-1],e.fragment&&e.fragment.p(e.ctx,t),e.after_update.forEach(O)}}function X(e){const t=[],n=[];x.forEach(r=>e.indexOf(r)===-1?t.push(r):n.push(r)),n.forEach(r=>r()),x=t}const Z=new Set;function ee(e,t){e&&e.i&&(Z.delete(e),e.i(t))}function te(e,t,n,r){const{fragment:s,after_update:o}=e.$$;s&&s.m(t,n),r||O(()=>{const i=e.$$.on_mount.map(H).filter(S);e.$$.on_destroy?e.$$.on_destroy.push(...i):$(i),e.$$.on_mount=[]}),o.forEach(O)}function ne(e,t){const n=e.$$;n.fragment!==null&&(X(n.after_update),$(n.on_destroy),n.fragment&&n.fragment.d(t),n.on_destroy=n.fragment=null,n.ctx=[])}function se(e,t){e.$$.dirty[0]===-1&&(v.push(e),U(),e.$$.dirty.fill(0)),e.$$.dirty[t/31|0]|=1<<t%31}function re(e,t,n,r,s,o,i,l=[-1]){const u=j;q(e);const a=e.$$={fragment:null,ctx:[],props:o,update:I,not_equal:s,bound:C(),on_mount:[],on_destroy:[],on_disconnect:[],before_update:[],after_update:[],context:new Map(t.context||(u?u.$$.context:[])),callbacks:C(),dirty:l,skip_bound:!1,root:t.target||u.$$.root};i&&i(a.root);let p=!1;if(a.ctx=n?n(e,t.props||{},(f,y,...b)=>{const Q=b.length?b[0]:y;return a.ctx&&s(a.ctx[f],a.ctx[f]=Q)&&(!a.skip_bound&&a.bound[f]&&a.bound[f](Q),p&&se(e,f)),y}):[],a.update(),p=!0,$(a.before_update),a.fragment=r?r(a.ctx):!1,t.target){if(t.hydrate){const f=W(t.target);a.fragment&&a.fragment.l(f),f.forEach(P)}else a.fragment&&a.fragment.c();t.intro&&ee(e.$$.fragment),te(e,t.target,t.anchor,t.customElement),M()}q(u)}class oe{$destroy(){ne(this,1),this.$destroy=I}$on(t,n){if(!S(n))return I;const r=this.$$.callbacks[t]||(this.$$.callbacks[t]=[]);return r.push(n),()=>{const s=r.indexOf(n);s!==-1&&r.splice(s,1)}}$set(t){this.$$set&&!K(t)&&(this.$$.skip_bound=!0,this.$$set(t),this.$$.skip_bound=!1)}}function F(e){let t,n=e[0].answers[1].answer+"",r,s,o;return{c(){t=g("button"),r=J(n),k(t,"class","btn-primary-no svelte-728kd")},m(i,l){D(i,t,l),m(t,r),s||(o=Y(t,"click",e[5]),s=!0)},p(i,l){l&1&&n!==(n=i[0].answers[1].answer+"")&&T(r,n)},d(i){i&&P(t),s=!1,o()}}}function B(e){let t,n=e[0].answers[2].answer+"",r,s,o;return{c(){t=g("button"),r=J(n),k(t,"class","btn-primary-no guardian svelte-728kd")},m(i,l){D(i,t,l),m(t,r),s||(o=Y(t,"click",e[6]),s=!0)},p(i,l){l&1&&n!==(n=i[0].answers[2].answer+"")&&T(r,n)},d(i){i&&P(t),s=!1,o()}}}function ie(e){let t,n,r,s,o=e[0].question+"",i,l,u,a=e[0].answers[0].answer+"",p,f,y,b,Q,c=e[0].answers[1]&&F(e),d=e[0].answers[2]&&B(e);return{c(){t=g("main"),n=g("div"),r=g("div"),s=g("p"),i=J(o),l=E(),u=g("button"),p=J(a),f=E(),c&&c.c(),y=E(),d&&d.c(),k(s,"class","card-text svelte-728kd"),k(u,"class","btn-primary svelte-728kd"),u.disabled=e[1],k(r,"class","card-body svelte-728kd"),k(n,"class","card")},m(h,w){D(h,t,w),m(t,n),m(n,r),m(r,s),m(s,i),m(r,l),m(r,u),m(u,p),m(r,f),c&&c.m(r,null),m(r,y),d&&d.m(r,null),b||(Q=Y(u,"click",e[3]),b=!0)},p(h,[w]){w&1&&o!==(o=h[0].question+"")&&T(i,o),w&1&&a!==(a=h[0].answers[0].answer+"")&&T(p,a),w&2&&(u.disabled=h[1]),h[0].answers[1]?c?c.p(h,w):(c=F(h),c.c(),c.m(r,y)):c&&(c.d(1),c=null),h[0].answers[2]?d?d.p(h,w):(d=B(h),d.c(),d.m(r,null)):d&&(d.d(1),d=null)},i:I,o:I,d(h){h&&P(t),c&&c.d(),d&&d.d(),b=!1,Q()}}}function ae(e,t,n){let r=[{id:0,question:`Hi, I'm jen 
 I may be having a recurring medical event 
 Please follow the prompts BEFORE calling 911. 
 Will you consent to help me?`,answers:[{answer:"Touch here for Yes",nextQuestion:1},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:12}]},{question:"Am I breathing?",id:1,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:2},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:18}]},{question:"Does breathing seem difficult?",id:2,answers:[{answer:"No",nextQuestion:3},{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:10}]},{question:"Everything is probably ok. This is likely a regular medical event for Jen not a 911 call message.",id:3,answers:[{answer:"Touch here for next",nextQuestion:4}]},{question:"Am I awake/conscious?",id:4,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:5},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:15}]},{question:"am I coherent/making sense?",id:5,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:6},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:7}]},{id:6,question:"Try to communicate with me and hit next when told to do so.",answers:[{answer:"Touch here for next",nextQuestion:7}]},{question:"Am I Moving?",id:7,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:13},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:8}]},{question:"Do I seem cold?",id:8,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:16},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:9}]},{question:"Do I seem warm?",id:9,answers:[{answer:"Yes",nextQuestion:17},{answer:"No",nextQuestion:19}]},{id:10,question:"Jen has several breathing problems. This is normal for Jen. Please help Jen support the bottom of her ribcage and wait for the timer to end.",type:240,answers:[{answer:"Touch here for next",nextQuestion:11}]},{id:11,question:"find ___ for additional help.",answers:[{answer:"Touch here for details",nextQuestion:2e3}]},{id:12,question:"Touch here to call 911.  Please share that Jen might be having a medical event and has recurring health problems. ",answers:[{answer:"Touch here to call 911!",nextQuestion:91111111}]},{id:13,question:"Jen has atypical absence seizures. This is normal for Jen. Do not call 911 unless she’s convulsing (not normal) or is visibly bleeding. Please remain calm. Being comforting as you might to a child is helpful. If Jen is confused, terrified, or otherwise upset, that’s okay. The seizure has passed and Jen is in recovery mode. Jen may not know herself, may be stuttering, or may be entirely nonverbal. Her brain is rebooting. Water, time, sleep is the only cure. Have her drink some water, and herd her towards one of the wellness rooms once she’s able to stutter in a few minutes. Everything’s fine. ",answers:[{answer:"If Jen is particularly upset, click here to play her some personally soothing audio. <insert link here>"},{answer:"Does Jen look confused at communication attempts? Click here to view the sign language alphabet.",nextQuestion:14},{answer:"Have you been preselected as a guardian to help Jen get home? Click here for details",nextQuestion:20}]},{id:14,question:" I live across the street at the Residence Inn. Room 524. Key should be in my jacket pocket or the pocket of whatever bag I brought today. After a seizure, I’m a little frightened of things in motion, like elevators or cars. Please don’t use my last name or the word home. Please understand that I currently have no filter and will not remember much later. Please be patient."},{id:15,type:30,question:"Please wait one minute. A link to call 911 will automatically appear after one minute.  If I do not regain consciousness, or am screaming while unconscious, please call 911 and share that I have absence seizures, cerebral palsy, asthma/restrictive thoracic disorder and periodic partial paralysis.",answers:[{answer:"Touch here if I wake up",nextQuestion:7}]},{id:16,question:"Jen has periodic partial paralysis. This is normal for Jen. Please help Jen get warmer, especially her hands, neck, and upper legs. It will take some time for Jen to recover; however, once warmer, she will be fully communicative."},{id:17,question:"Jen has periodic partial paralysis. This is normal for Jen. Please help Jen get cooler, especially her neck, hands, and forehead. Ice or wet paper towels help.  It will take some time for Jen to recover; however, once cooler, she will be fully communicative. "},{id:18,question:"Touch here to call 911. Please share that Jen is having a medical event and has cerebral palsy, asthma/restrictive thoracic disorder, absence seizures, and periodic partial paralysis. ",answers:[{answer:"click here to call 911!",nextQuestion:91111111}]},{id:19,question:"Touch here to call 911. This is not a normal medical event for Jen. Please share that Jen is having a medical event and has cerebral palsy, asthma/restrictive thoracic disorder, absence seizures, and periodic partial paralysis.",answers:[{answer:"click here to call 911!",nextQuestion:91111111}]}],s=r[0],o=9,i=()=>{(s.id===12||s.id===18||s.id===19)&&(window.location.href="tel:911"),n(0,s=r[s.answers[0].nextQuestion]),clearTimeout(o),console.log(o," - current timer id"),console.log("timeoutwas just cleareed with temp func")},l=s,u=()=>{n(4,l=s),console.log(l,"qDuringCallFunc"),console.log(s,"currentQuestionFunc"),l==s&&console.log(!0)},a=!1;const p=()=>n(0,s=r[s.answers[1].nextQuestion]),f=()=>n(0,s=r[s.answers[2].nextQuestion]);return e.$$.update=()=>{e.$$.dirty&17&&s.type&&(console.log("this question has a type"),u(),o=setTimeout(()=>{console.log("2 seconds ran"),l==s&&n(0,s=r[s.answers[0].nextQuestion])},s.type*1e3)),e.$$.dirty&1&&s.id===10&&(n(1,a=!0),setTimeout(()=>{n(1,a=!1)},3e4))},[s,a,r,i,l,p,f]}class le extends oe{constructor(t){super(),re(this,t,ae,ie,R,{})}}new le({target:document.getElementById("app")});
